Inventory of the Augustus C. Golding Papers 1859-1934, 1862-1864
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Typescripts n.d., 3 items. (Box 2)
  - n.p. Typed transcript of copybook of Augustus C. Golding's Civil War letters, n.d., 157 pages. Ts of Cy of ALS. (Box 2)
    Typed transcript of copybook of Augustus C. Golding's Civil War letters to "Friend Cumming" or "My Dear Madam" [Mrs. Cumming]. May 1862-9 September 1864. Preface, epilogue, and end notes by Ralph Poriss.
  - n.p. Typed transcript of Augustus C. Golding's three Civil War diaries, n.d., 122 pages. Ts of AD. (Box 2)
    22 November 1861-7 November 1864. Incomplete. Missing 8 November 1864-25 November 1864. Also missing additional entries written by Golding, 28 February 1901-23 November 1908.